The talent painter who could draw
outlook about cap without rim.
Mao drawing is beautiful
It is beautiful.
I am ashamed.
You also finish your drawing hurry.
I remember I have something to do,
wait for me, I will come back.
What
You ask me bring beautiful drawing like
photo
It's boring.
Why?
If you want a drawing like photo
you could take a photo.
All drawing is beautiful.
You must show it after you finished.
After all watch, they will make fun of
me.
I see. After all watch it, they
must make fun of you.
OK. Let I help you.
Good.
14th pencil, you could use it draw
this outlook.
Follow the man who wear cap watch
though rim to touch pencil and receive
message
then order your finger and muscle
And don't care its theory.
Anyway
you could draw outlook same as human
watch.
Let's try.
Dad is sleeping.
Never mind.
Then put pencil and sketch on his hand
He is drawing outlook he dream.
It is unimaginable.
He take a big pot, and he is so happy
What is he dreaming?
About fore case, if he remembered, he
could draw.
I adjust it and let he draw what
happened before five minutes.
Oh, it is he won at golf match.
Let me try.
It is good...
In this case, it hasn't problem.
Good, I leave.
Who is the man just now?
What's wrong with mama?
That man smiled and said hello to me
when he glanced aside me just now
As if I ever met him
If you use it to draw, you will remember
But mama don't know to draw.
Never mind, wear it
Could you draw?
Strange, my hand draw intransitively.
How come? Strange.
Drawing is good.
I don't know that mama has this skill.
Thank you.
Yi, the man is minister's wife of our
company.
My stars! I should be more polite to
say hello.
It's convenient that I could use it by
anywhere.
Boy, where is station?
There.
Right
Why is he hurry-scurry?
Bad...
If here is that...
What?
It is that...
You make me in a stew.
It's me.
Well, use this drawing
What?
Good, it's okay like this.
How weird, I don't know drawing.
It's good, I am happy.
It's police office.
It's that...
You couldn't remember police office,
you are hurry-scurry man.
What did you do when you went to
police office.
Well, I lost that thing, it's that...
Please draw.
You draw well again, I'm happy.
Portfolio
What?
There is ten million in the portfolio.
I forgot to take it.
Where did it?
Let me from the bottom up.
Well, in the telephone booth.
I finished call and forgot to take port-
folio, I remembered it on my way home
When I went back
portfolio hasn't been there.
Who took it
It's good if someone saw it.
Well.
Are you here at all times?
So, please you draw.
Dog draw.
Before ten minutes, the portfolio
was in the telephone box.
Please draw what in it every 11 seconds.
That man took it.
What? The man ran to station just now.
Run back over, he looks like goat.
Anyway, let us go to police office first
What should we do about my portfolio.
Ten million?
Yes.
COP-
Have you seen that man?
Ten million. The portfolio has ten
million.
The man was there.
Get it, that is my portfolio.
Get it, Ms...
The portfolio was left in telephone box
the man sent it here.
The portfolio sticked with dirt.
Dangerous, I almost make a mistake.
I think there is police box near station
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You do me a good turn to much.
Good.
Well, I forgot to draw.
Well, let me draw here.
I will finish to draw at once.
It's simple.
What, this drawing has been drawn by
Nobita
Like photo.
However, it likes photo.
You are idiot.
Because you drew bed, you sticked photo.
No, I drew it by myself.
Yes, I drew it by myself.
Let's go. OK.
Wait...
Don't joke. Ouch!
You are go to far.
Shizuka's belt.
Refund it to me.
No.
Please, refund it to me.
Please.
I say no.
If I haven't that belt, I won't be
able to return heaven.
Please refund belt to me.
I will take it away as my storehouse.
Ha...
Doraemon
Nobita, you are go to far.
Ouch.
Hurry to refund, only thieves
take other thing.
Doraemon, this is...
You are shameful. Don't swing the lead
again.
No, you make a mistake. Doraemon
Actually...
You are rehearsing
Yes.
Schoolmate rehearse statedly
so we are rehearsing.
I see.
It isn't joke. You stroked my head.
Sorry...
Jeez. Doraemon, you are immodest.
Well, what are you rehearse?
We are rehearsing fairy belt.
We are thinking how to finish.
Now the gut is she ask me refund belt
to her.
And let return heaven.
But we can't rehearse favorably
Doraemon, what is your idea?
Return heaven... Well
I lend you a goods.
Good goods. Yes.
It fit this drama.
Light belt.
Nice.
You flow it over, let me see.
I know.
How come?
I can hike up...
Cool...
Like fairy.
Doraemon, thank you.
It will be a arresting drama.
I am also happy that I could help you.
Fly high more and more,
the wind will be stronger.
Help.
Oh, you just take the belt away.
Shizuka disappeared.
Where is she?
As if she flied in the mount.
Well, where is the belt?
If I haven't the belt...
Gel it.
It is magic belt.
It's my first time to watch it.
I will take it as my family's treasure.
Wait... that is my belt, please
refund it to me.
No.
I found it.
No, it isn't unfair.
I won't go home if I haven't the belt.
I will refund it to you if you dance.
As if it likes guts more and more.
I ever studied ballet
but I couldn't dance if I haven't music.
If sing, leave it to me.
There is a river before my house.
There is a sidehill behind my house.
There are some wide flowers in the
sidehill.
Wide flower is red like fire.
There are gooses in the river.
Gooses are playing in the river.
They are happy-
and sing
How about it?
I dance ballet follow nursery rhyme.
I refund belt to you.
Yi, where is the belt put it here?
Jeez...
I can't go home if I haven't belt.
Mr. Hou, please give it back me.
Wait.
Belt, wait.
The belt is so lightsome and willowy.
Yes.
As child nappy, it is the best.
It's good like this.
Son...
Son.
Where did the belt fly?
It's troublesome
Shizuka
Where is she?
Son... Son, where are you?
Bell...
Son...
Ouch.
She is there.
Son... Belt...
Son
Nobita
Good.
As if we have settled favorably.
Yes. Belt has come back safely.
Good.
If we should tell her
that belt has been used as nappy.
I will flow this belt over and become
a beautiful fairy in the drama.
I think we don't tell her.
Yes.
I will show as a beautiful fairy.
All will applaud for me.
Draw cartoon in can
Shizuka's gill cartoon drawing is good.
Gian's wrestling cartoon drawing has
force.
That is my normal cartoon.
Nobita's cartoon is abstract.
If you forgot that today is the last
day to receive contribution.
By inches
Because I lost pushfulness,
I couldn't design a good result.
Well, come to my house.
My mama is out today, there isn't person
No.,,
Only by inches. I go home and bring it.
My house is quiet.
Thank you... I will finish soon.
Hey, you are conscienceless.
We only wait for you an hour, you must
hurry.
I know.
It is troublesome.
Let's do cartoon magazine.
It's funny.
Today is the last day to receive
contribution.
We must obey the rule.
Otherwise it will make all trouble.
I am drawing.
We take it to them.
You aren't distortionist
You drew bed, it is little thing.
If you are try best to draw...
But it is bad.
I have given up.
It's my fault.
So I lend you a goods.
Cartoon paper.
If you use your impression,
it will appear pattern you want.
Good, like handwork.
It's simple and out of a clear sky,
right?
If I have way-out cartoon
I could draw.
You must be serious.
If you think another at same time
they will mix.
The first episode is space shuttle fly
in space.
Nobita, I need your help.
Please buy something for mama.
Shit.
It mix in picture.
This paper is light.
Original, it is well-off.
Let me redraw.
Space shuttle is cool...
Reclaim old newspaper, magazine
He come again, jeez...
There are old newspaper
I can't draw intently.
Well, bring it out.
Empty can.
I prepared this workroom for writer,
so he could write intently.
Only close the cover. Except you
use opener, you couldn't open it.
It should fine like this.
Cheer up.
Is Nobita-sensei home? Has he finished
drawing?
He is drawing now. He will finish soon.
Please tell him hurry.
Because we can't publish magazine.
I know. When he finished, he will send
it.
Nobita that guy hasn't finished.
Must be.
What?
He hasn't finished, why?
Because I don't know how to design.
I can't think out good idea.
Because I am anxious, so I can't think
out.
What should I do you will be satisfying.
Cartoon original
There are some matter of story in it.
As if there are various of role
about A or B.
You will finish if you add some roles
you created in it.
But I couldn't create any roles.
Really?
If you design the lead role is
handsome and brave.
And reverse role is a troublesome
man with snotty face.
Base on your friend, you will could draw
OK.
I have some image.
Doraemon, hurry to bring can out.
If you are slow, you will late.
I should be able to finish this time.
The lead role is me.
It become to emerge
and change same as my thought.
Continue.
Suneo and Gian are the villain.
Gian is fulsome in the cartoon
I can draw continually after I accept it
It's funny.
Continue.
You defeated Suneo and Gian now.
So you are complacent.
You drew you was cool
and drew us was villain.
You guy!
What's wrong with Nobita?
Time is late
we won't wait for him.
Let me see.
In either case, he mustn't finish to
draw.
Do you finish?
Uh.
Good.
Draw good.
The lead role become weak in the
story process.
Why will bad man become stronger.
Slowly.
Never mind, hurry to hand it in.
It's funny.
Nobita draw well.
Really?
No idea.Nobita is puzzled
The nature in the room
Great,I want to go there
Doraemon, Mum is not in home today
We rebuild the room in the hills
Live in the surrounding of the nature
Turn the room to mountain
Ok,it is no problem
For the youth who has not been
taken out to play in the holiday
Speaking of that
Then you must clean the room
I see
Leave it to me
Meadow rug
The camp with outlook
Steadier with trees
So smart
It like the nature more and more
The radiation rays
...can model the sunlight and the
running cloud
...feel the wind of the nature
It is a bird
That is machine bird
That is machine butterfly
And machine
Great.
I can not believe we are in the
center of the city
It make us ease
I am the clerk of the grocery, come for
money
You break the air
That is the book closet,here is the exit
How pain,I am enjoy the good feeling
Mother is not in,please come later
Ok
Doraemon
I found I can hear a lot of sound
The sound of the radio,of the cars.
...of the morning exercises,and of the
dogs
Yes,it is
Use this to get rid of the sound
This is the river rug
It is so smart
It is so cool,so comfort
Right
Excuse me,I am from the morning paper
Come for the newspaper
My mother is not in,please come later
How comfort
I am form the noodle shop,come for money
He come again,Doraemon,
cast about for it
Then let the guest in
Excuse me,ls Nobita in?
Shizuka
That is waterfall wallpaper
You can come in from the yard
The head is big
It is bright when he hang his head
What's up?
I am Doraemon
He is the machine cat form the future
world
I have to go out for a moment
You can not do anything string to the
mountain
Strange mountain
Such as regard here as the hike field
Gather 10 yuan each,such things
Don't do that
Right
Good idea,why I have not got it
Come to raise a stake
The forest is beckon to you
You will reach the mountain after
1 minute's walk
Really?
Of course,you will not feel you are in
home
Welcome
Only 10 yuan
Rally
Here is very pretty
Haha
You made a stake
They are quarrelling,no way
That is ..
Don't do that,because we are in the room
The campfire is rising
It is tragedy if the fire in home
There is the fire?
What are you doing?
I make the campfire,everyone is happy
Yes.
What are you doing?
Mum is going home
Bad,go back quickly
Go back home
Why you treat the guests this way?
I paid 10 yuan
Let me play longer
Clear away,quickly
We catch at once
What happened in the room?
You will not get the dinner until
you clear it away!
It is not a good thing that Jiaxing
has not taken the rubbish back
I see
The liquid fecit the force scope
Nobita,that is not my fault
What are you saying?I will catch you
Wait,not run
Geez
I catch him by inches
Remember I will beat you heavier
He has gone
You have a lot of sweat
I am frightened
I don't know whether I can avoid
Gian's beat and back home
It doesn't matter
It is the mostly the sports quantity
You are derelict of duty
Think while put yourself in the
position of the one be runner
50"'!
It is better if there are more place
to hide
It seems a safe place
Then distinguish the scope
Doesn't the dog wander and pipit?
That is the announce
It told other dog,here is it's land
Just like the sparrow vie the land
Or while troll the fish
Driving other fish out of its land
But tempt it
And many other animal has its scope
So while they fighting
It will win in his land
Then what do you want to take out
I have not idea
Just this
The liquid drew the scope
What's that?So cool
I will not lend to you since do need
not it
I see
If only you drop the liquid on the
ground
You can draw your own scope
With this?
Pick up form the top
Ok,I will comet try
Strange,it will not drop out
It must stick here
First grovel,upraise a foot
It is the same with the doggy
It is ashamed,I will not do it
This way?
Don't lose time in doing it
It will be invalidate 10 meters away
I have spew the liquid
It will be no problem no matter who
come
I don't understand
You will know then
Nobita why not to buy things
Geez
I forgot,I will do it now
No problem
Now you are in your own scope
Geez
Mum called you too today
Mum,what do you want to do today?
Nothing
Then why you upraise your hand'?
I don't know either
Don't cry so loud if there is nothing
You will bother the neighborhood
50"'!
Mum is so prolixity
Last time Mum ..
Nobita...
But tempt it
You scarce me to death
You need not scarce if only you have
the scale
I see
Next time I will make the scale outside
First drop between the door and the
electric pole
No one see
No,drop quickly
Ok,that's ok
Here is your scale
Has anyone come?
Nobita
Wait. No problem
No problem?
No problem.
You ..
Oddball
Do you have any business with me ?
Answer me quickly
You spite me every time,could it funny?
No.Nobita,I don't mean that
Then get away quickly
50"'!
I won,unbelievable
Then you believe the effect of the scale
You make my scale
Impossible
If only I stand in the scale
Then I need not afraid of anyone
Damned,remember
If well done.l need not afraid the dog
There is only one pole left
My scale will be clone with the liquid
Nobita
What are you doing,the strange post
I lost something here or square
Where is the diamond
Bad
I will help you
No.thanks,Shizuka,I will do it myself
Let me help you
No use
Nothing,we should help each other
No thanks.So hard
You the guy
No.no use
Shizuka,you need not look for it
Go aside
Nobita,help
Pill forcing weight
I am full
Are you full
Eh,let's go
Geez,there are so much rice and dished
left
Let the kid be
Not cherish the food
I must say to him
Nobita
I have something to tell you
Any business?
When Paw is a child,the America is in
the war
Yes,fight
Have you hear me
Are you in the action then?
Yes.
What did I want to say to you?
Right
We have nothing to eat in the war
Even eat locust and fibril
How fun
Any fun?
All are hungry,then
Faint everyday
Ok
Yes,this way
Beat the opponent quickly
Do him.quickly
Did you listen to others seriously?
Paw.what are you angry for ?
Because you do not cherish he food
But we have a lot,nothing
But you should waste it
Yes,beat him
Just there
This way,beat quickly
To the one who does not know hungry and
pain
It is not use to say that
Yes
What he said is right
Human can not go without food
You must cherish
Ok
Go on beating
Heavier
It is better to let she know the pain
of hungry
Pill of losing weight
The pill is to reduce the quantity of
food
One pill will make you can not eat on
dinner
Have it .one pill is ok
Beat.
So smart
You eat it later
One pill is ok
Fun
What's that?
Doraemon
How fun
It is to late to
...to to school
Pain
Nobita,eat bread and milk
Now we have no time to eat this
We are going to late
The effect is appear
He do not want to have the dinner
He must like to eat
He will know of the happy of eating
Delicious
I am home
Good smile
Froth noodle,
So mean,even not leaving some soup
The dinner is
I have not eat
Why?
For I want to WC before the dinner
I was locked in for 1 hour
Mum,cook something to me ,anything is ok
She is out and will come back later
Where is the cake?
Noting is prepared,for she is anxious
I come to eat instant noodle
That one is the last one
Ok,wait to the supper
Go to buy a bread
How can you have a rest?
Here is the place for rest
All the shop is having rest
Too much
I am so hungry
It is juice
It has not drop down
Even the money
Return me the money
Money..
Don't broke the things
I am more honey
Nobita
Play the cheese together
Ok.
You will forget the
General
Geez
You are conered
It is dark
It is the time for dinner,I am home
Wait,I will flee
I will play until I win
I see
I am hungry
I seems win
You must not lose to me on purpose
I won again
Once more
I will win
I won again
Once more
Mum,where is the supper?
It is ok
It is so late,where are you going?
Supper
You need not eat,for you can not finish
Mum,I am hungry,I want to eat
Nobita,you missed the time of lunch
You eat more than one pill
Almost 10 pill
You will have nothing to eat in 3 days
I don't want ..
I will die
I don't want to die
I am hungry
Will I starve?
Too stretch the the truth!
But..
The good steam break,I will have a bite
This is my head
Bad smile
No way
We can only back to 4 days later,
let them eat something first
The noodle are good thing
Nobita,is it you who eat the noodles
No
This evening I will not give you food
I am still being scold 4 days later
It seems the pills work
Don't worry it
Eat and flee
But I am worry about
Don't mind too much
Only that you have the food to eat is ok
But
The story with the disaster around
So pain
What happened?
Alas
What is going on today?
So pain
What's up?
I walk on the road and bump the
electric pole
So stolidity
What the stolidity ?
So pain
Geez,I always bump or tumble
Really?
Why I am so unlucky?
It is not the problem of luck
You have not pay much attention
No.l am no luck
If I know it earlier,
I can avoid it
Do you have any good thing
No idea
If you know the disaster
ls there any good thing?
This
The preteller of disaster
Yes,it is the alert equipment
But rather be more careful in the
common
...then to rely on the thing
Be more careful
And your worst problem is
It is missing
Let you be
Try with this thumbpin
I will stamp on the thumbpin if I go
straight
And I check wither the bell ring or not
So smart
It will be ok with it
Wonderful
Now I can walk peacefully
Turn to me if there is anything
It seems something happen here, go
away quickly
But it is dangerous
No one is there
ls there any blunder stone
There is no cars passed
No one bite me
Then go to have a look
What it is on earth
How pain
50"'!
Are you all right
Yes,I do feel pain
The machine works
You scarce me to death
Do believe the bell
What's this?
Do you refer Gian
I prefell not well
Hide up quickly
Suneo,have you seen Nobita
What's wrong with Nobita
Nobita told my mother that I have
beaten him
Too far away,give him a good lesson
Of course,let me know if you meet him
Ok.
I will give him a good lesson
Sure enough there is disaster
Goodbye
Stay at home peacefully
There are
Go back home quickly
Have you seen Nobita
Dangerous
It is bad to walk this road
It is Nobita,go to tell Gian quickly
Horrible
It ring again
Doraemon,do you know where
Nobita has gone
He is out ,how are you?
He even drop the thumbpin in the
corridor
I will give him a good lesson when he
comes back
Geez.
So hard,there is disaster there
Fortunately we have the teller
Incredibly it is Doraemon,I like
him more
This way,bad,go quickly
This way
Bad
What to do?
Have a rest here
Feddle-dee-dee
He is astonished again
Shut up
Baby is asleep but awake by you
50"'!
Damn“
Tomorrow I will have a test, you make me
fuss
Sorry,I leave now
Sure enough Nobita can not avoid the
disaster
Miniwind
Strong Miniwind
Good wind
This is the machine of storing wind
There is a lot of wind there
Where is the wind last night
Yes
Give out some
What is this
It has a lot of usage
What's wrong?
Because the wind last night is strange
I will help you in the direction control
Can you?
If only unscrew
Thank you
I can take the place of energy
But I hope he won't extra-speed
Don't run
Don't run,thief
Damn“
Sir,you can sun him with this
stop
I caught the guy
So the thief can not escape
Because of the typhoon,a lot of leaves
dropped
Ok,use it to clean
Ok
Begin
It is clean
It can be used as clean tool
So convenient
Nobita
What are you doing,it seems funny
Let me look
No.it is dangerous if you use it
careless
What are you saying?
You don't want to lend me?
Strong wind
Maybe the balloon can fly up
Ok,we try it,Doraemon
Ok
Because of the typhoon,you must careful
Be careful
Then I will begin
First unlock the screw
H'! up great
Let us fly up
Unscrew the screw
It is Nobita
Let us fly up
Nobita...
Shizuka
I will not lose it
Wait me
Come up quickly
Damint,he did not look for me,Geez,wait
How fun!
Fly higher
Higher
Fun
I will use all this
Gian
We run after him
Save me
Gian
I can not run
Until the wind finished,
Save me
He flied a whole night,so cold
That's because he use is careless
Look,he flower and the grass
Every one
So we walk happily
And sing happily
We are human
Planet in the university
It is the country full of dreams and
smile faces
We walk together
We are human being
Today or tomorrow or the day after
tomorrow
We create together
The city full of dreams